Andre Defremont

Belém, Pará, Brazil



andre.def93@gmail.com



+5591981348438



linkedin.com/in/andredefremont

Summary

Full Stack Developer since 2012, experienced in Node.js, NoSQL Databases, Vue.js, React.js and Blockchain related techs like Hyperledger Fabric.

Bachelor of Information Systems, wich had contributed to the Blockchain scenario trought a published research about: "Decentralized Autonomous Software Publisher" with Hyperledger Fabric.

My interests are develop, manage e lead projects that have high value proposition on sustainable and tech way.

defremont.github.io | github.com/defremont | andre@amachains.com | gitlab.com/defremont

Experience



Diretor de informações

Amachains

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

- Blockchain Network
- AWS / EC2 / Kubes
- Vue.is
- Angular 7/8
- Hyperledger

Software Developer

Equilibrium Web

Jul 2019 - Mar 2020 (9 months)

- Angular 4/5
- Java
- JSF
- SpringBoot
- Ionic

Analyst & Developer

Xifix

Apr 2018 - Jul 2019 (1 year 4 months)

- UI/UX experience
- Clean design
- React.js / Redux

Web Developer

Universidade Federal do Pará

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Responsible for the planning and development of an innovative look for the former portal of a college institute.

- CSS HTML JS
- Joomla
- PostgreSQL

ฅ Co-founder & Full Stack Node.js

Agência Digital CastleDev 2013 - 2018 (6 years)

Digital Marketing & Developer

Onbyte

Jun 2012 - Jul 2016 (4 years 2 months)

- CSS HTML, JS
- React.js / Redux
- Node.js

RCA - Representante Comercial Autônomo

Barsa Planeta Jul 2011 - Aug 2011 (2 months)

Education



🛓 Universidade Federal do Pará

Bacharelado em Sistemas de Informação, Blockchain 2013 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications



- Gestor de Marketing Digital e Mídias Sociais OAJ Gestão de Marketing
- PNL Programação Neuro Linguística Barsa Planeta
- Semana OminiStack 11 Rocketseat
- NASA Space Apps Challenge Brazil 2020 Space Labs Brazil
- Voluntário SBC Sociedade Brasileira de Computação SBC

- Registro de Programa de Computador INPI Brasil Instituto Nacional da Propriedade Industrial
- The Complete Node.js Developer Course (3rd Edition) Udemy UC-04b800ea-a2e6-4b60-bab7-670badd1aff4
- **Nuxt.js Vue.js on Steroids** Udemy UC-bf95f4ec-81ec-4454-a82b-9f3841f5a961
- Vue The Complete Guide (w/ Router, Vuex, Composition API) Udemy UC-1100a4bf-1a6a-463d-a0c9-6d8af40cb30b

Skills

Blockchain • Vue.js • Progressive Web Apps (PWA) • Information Technology • Project Management • IT Strategy • Desenvolvimento de sites • Planejamento estratégico • Desenvolvimento de software • Web design